Guide to the Yoshio Kishi and Irene Yah-Ling Sun Collection 1860-2010 MSS.292
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series IV: Hollywood Films, Television, Theater, and Actors
  - Subseries A: Film
    - Binder - Unlabeled ("Stills"), Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Binder - "19 AMW 1922; 20 1929", Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Binder - "21" (1 of 2), Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Binder - "21" (2 of 2), Undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Binder - "Notes", Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Binder - Unlabeled (1 of 2), Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Binder - Unlabeled (2 of 2), Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Binder - Unlabeled [2] (1 of 2), Undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Binder - Unlabeled [2] (2 of 2), Undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Berlin Alexanderplatz - film program, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Berlin Alexanderplatz - NY Times article, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - The Cable Guide, October 1985 (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Catalog - historical films, 1894-1915, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - "Charlie Chan and the Curse of the Dragon Queen" screenplay, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Charlie Chan movie stills, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Cineaste, vol. IX, no. 3, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Cinema, vol. 6, no. 1, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Cinéma 56, vol. II, no. 8, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Cinemages, 1955, 1957, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - "The Cliffdwellers" screenplay, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - A Collector's Guide to Movie Memorabilia, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Corinth Films, vol. 1, no. 1, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Eastman Kodak Company Motion Picture Films, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Editors Guild Magazine, 2006 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Factfile: Movie and TV Nostalgia, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Festival of Women's Films, 1975-1976 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Festival of Women's Films, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Filmmaker's Monthly, vol. 14, no. 12, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Film Bill, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Film Fan Monthly, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Films for Television, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Films from Britain, Undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Films in Review, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - The Film Journal, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Film play, vol. I, no. 11, May 1922 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Film Quarterly, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Film Society - Theodore Huff Memorial, 1960 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Gallery of Picture Players, October 1912 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - "Hollywood" vol. 21, no. 2, 1932 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - "Hollywood" vol. 26, no. 12, 1938 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - The Hollywood Reporter, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - "The Honorable Mr. Wong" film flyer, Undated (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - In Cinema, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - In Performance, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom - story book, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Ito, Robert B. - "A Brief History of Hollywood Yellowface", 2003 (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Japanese Film Advertisement, Undated (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - The Journal of Popular Film, vol. 3, no. 1, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Kong News, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - "Licensed to Kill" flyer with note written on it, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - "Lincoln Center's Sixth New York Film Festival" program, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Lobby Cards (catalog), Undated (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - "Martial Arts Movies", 1982 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - "Making Films in New York", 1969 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Minorities and the Media, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Motion Picture Magazine, vol. XV, no. 3; vol. XLII, no. 3, 1918, 1931 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Motion Picture Magazine, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Motion Picture Magazine, vol. XXVIII, no. 10 (1 of 2), 1924 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Motion Picture Magazine, vol. XXVIII, no. 10 (2 of 2), 1924 (Box 14, Folder 39)
    - Motion Picture Magazine, vol. XXXVI, no. 6, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - "Movie" no. 13, 1965 (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - Movieline, 2001 (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - Movies for TV, 6900 Ratings, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - Movie Weekly, vol. II, nos. 41, 47, 1922 (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Moving Picture Stories, 1913, 1917, 1922, 1923 (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - The Moving Picture Weekly, vol 9, no. 21, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - The Museum of Modern Art Film Library - publications, 1959, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - News Reel, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - New York Post TV Week, 1978 (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - On Location, 1980 (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - On Production, vol. 1, no. 1, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Pantomime, vol. 1, no. 7, 1921 (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Photoplay Magazine, January 1915 (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Photoplay Magazine, November 1915 (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Photoplay Magazine, March 1916 (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Photoplay Magazine, June 1916 (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Photoplay Magazine, October 1916 (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Photoplay Magazine, December 1916 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Photoplay Magazine, July 1919 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Photoplay Magazine, June 1923 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Photoplay Magazine, June 1924 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Picture Show, vol. 5, no. 106, 1921 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Picturegoer, vol. 19, no. 113, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Picturegoer 2d. vol. I, nos. 13, 21 (new series), 1931 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Police Film Magazine (French), 1938 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - "Racial Justice in Broadcasting" pamphlet, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Reel Life, vol. IX, no. 7, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "Rising Sun" advertisement, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - RKO Video, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Saddle Pals, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Saturday Review, 1962, 1966, 1967, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Screen Actors Guild Magazine, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Screen Book Magazine, April 1930 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Screen Nostalgia Illustrated, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Serial Pictorial no. 5 - Drums of Fu Manchu, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - She: The Magazine of Femme Fatale Cinema and Culture, vol. 2, no. 2, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - Shochiku Co. Ltd. stock list, Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Showbill, 1960 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Show Business Illustrated, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Sight and Sound, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - "Sixteen Millimeter Films" NYPL, 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Take One, vol. 7, no. 6, Undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Tokyo Joe, Undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Travel and Camera, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Tricycle: The Buddhist Review, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - TV Guide, 1973-1980 (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - The UNESCO Courrier, 1955, 1956, 1959 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Vietnam on Film and Television, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - "A Vicious Motive, Despicable Tricks - A Criticism of M. Anthony's Anti-China Fim 'China'" by Renmin Ribao, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Walt Disney Pictures presents 'Mulan' film credits, Undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Wayne Wang - screenplays - "Dim Sum" and "Chan is Missing", 1983 (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - White Slaves of Chinatown - brochure, Undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Wide Angle, vol. 4, no. 2, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Asian American International Film Festival - program [Flat Box], 1997 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Japanese Cinema flyer (in Japanese) [Flat Box], 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - "Topsy Turvy" ad in Variety Magazine [Flat Box], 2000 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Subseries B: Theater
    - Behind Enemy Lines - review, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Bunraku Puppet Theatre of Japan, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Chinese Acrobats and Magicians of Taiwan (playbill), 1979 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - The Chinese Theater, Undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Comedy in Chinese History and Manners - playbill and article, 1904 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Dance Magazine, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - "Double Dutch" materials and reviews, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Dralion: Cirque du Soleil, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - "The Drama in Chinatown" by Will Irwin in Everybody's Magazine, 1909 (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - The Drama Magazine, October 1930 (Box 15, Folder 46)
    - Flower Drum Song, Undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Forbidden City, USA - souvenir photos, Undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - The Grand Kabuki, 1982 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - IMAI - "The Winds of God" card, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - "Job's Passion" - NY Times article, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Kabuki Dance: Yaohan Waterside Plaza Grand Opening Commemorative Ceremony, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - La Mama Etc - programs, Undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Madame Butterfly: A Guide, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Madame Butterfly - program, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Manhattan Theatre Club, c. 1994 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Metropolitan Opera Fine Art Poster Collection (flyer), Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Metropolitan Opera Guild Engagement Calendar: Puccini, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Metropolitan Opera: Lincoln Center / stagebill, September 1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - "Miss Saigon" programs, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Mixed writings / plays, Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - The New York Times Television cover with Lee Majors in "Raven", 1992 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Opera News, 1953, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Pacific Overtures - programs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Pan Asian Repertory Theater, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Playbills, 1959-1988 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - The Play Pictorial, 1911, 1914 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - The Play Pictorial (photocopy), Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Play scripts - photocopies, Undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Santa Anita '42 - play by Allan Knee, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - South Pacific - program, Undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Theatre Arts, vol. XXVIII, no. 8, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Theatre Arts, 1948, 1949 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Theatre Arts Monthly, vol. XIV, no. 4, 1930 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Theatre Arts Monthly, 1931 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Theater Week, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - The World of Suzie Wong - Broadway show booklet, Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Subseries C: Actors
    - Aoki, Tsuru, Undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Bara, Theda - "The Soul of Buddha" review, 1918 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Chen, Joan - Twin Peaks, Undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue, Undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue - miscellaneous film-related material, 1915-1917, 1982, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue - oral history transcription, 1959 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue - Periodicals and clippings, 1917-1982 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue - Photocopies of various film-related material, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue - photographic material, Undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue - photographic material ("Prof. John Kuo Wei Tchen"), Undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue and Wong, Anna May - "Hollywood's Yellow Streak" by Harvey Elliot, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue and Wong, Anna May - stills from "Daughter of the Dragon", Undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Hepburn, Katherine - "Dragon Seed" stills, Undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Hines, Johnny - Chinatown Charlie advertisements, Undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Karloff, Boris - "The Mask of Fu Manchu" still, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Kuwa, George and Warner Oland - photographs and stills, 1926, Undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Kwan, Michelle - TV Guide, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Photocopies of various film-related materials, Undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Stroheim, Eric Von - headshot, Undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Wong, Anna May - bios, Undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Wong, Anna May - "China Doll" by Elizabeth Wong, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Wong, Anna May - "Daughter of the Orient" by Barrie Roberts, Undated (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Wong, Anna May - photocopies of film-related materials, Undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Wong, Anna May - photocopy of Certificate of Death, Last Will and Testament, Biography by Philip Leibfried, 1933, 1961, 2003 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Wong, Anna May - periodicals and clippings, Undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Wong, Anna May - photographic materials, Undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Wong, Anna May - photographic material, Undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Wray, Fay - oral history transcript, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Cho, Margaret - interview in "Lesbian News" [Flat Box], 2000 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue - scrapbook (1 of 2) [Flat Box], Undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Hayakawa, Sessue - scrapbook (2 of 2) [Flat Box], Undated (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - "Our Chinese Movie Actors" article [Flat Box], 1926 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Wong, Anna May - scrapbook [Flat Box], Undated (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Series V: Literature
  This series contains books and periodicals that have content pertaining to Asian Americans and Asian American themes.
  - Adventure, vol. 113, no. 3, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Abroad at Home, by Julian Street, 1915 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Anthology of Asian-American writings (collected by Kishi), Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Argosy Weekly, 1919, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Argosy Weekly, 1939 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Argosy Weekly, 1939, 1940, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Argosy Weekly, 1968, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - The Armchair Detective, 1979, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - The Armchair Detective, 1982, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Asia and the Humanities, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Baffling Detective Mysteries, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Bibliographies, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Book Revies - by Kishi for "The New York Nichibei", 1969-1982 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - "The Boy's Friend: Ching Lung's Wager, no. 294, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Bluebook, vol. 96, no. 1, 1952 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Cards / letters from review copies of books, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Comic Books, 1980, 1990, 1991, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Critique, vol. X, no. 2, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Detective Fiction Weekly, 1930, 1936 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Detective Story Magazine, 1926, 1927 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Detective Story Magazine, 1927 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Detective Story Magazine, 1928, 1929 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Dust jackets - "A Child in Prison Camp" and "Shinohata: a Portrait of a Japanese Village", Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Fiction, Asians in, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - The Guilty, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Haiku Harvest, annotated with quotes on book cover, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Harper's Magazine, 1921, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "Japanese Fiction" by Sadakichi Hartmann in the Forum, Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Lafcadio Hearn Journal, 1991-1995 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Leaves from Chinese History in Verse, Book 1, 1952 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - The Lion and the Unicorn, vol. 11, no. 1, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - The Master Detective, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - McClure's Magazine, 1908 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Mike Shayne Mystery Magazine, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Mrs. Spring Fragrance and Other Writings, by Sui Sin Far, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Modern Chinese Authors: a list of pseudonyms, 1969 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Mystery, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Mystery Magazine, 1941 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - The New Argosy, 1942 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - New Nick Carter Weekly, 1904 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - "Nothing Left in my Hands" book review, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Orientalism, Edward Said - afterword, Undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Parnassus, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Pearl Harbor: The Official 50th Anniversary Magazine, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Peter Piper's Tales about China, Undated (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Philo Vance: The Life and Times of S.S. Van Dine, by John Tuska, 1971 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - The Phoenix, vol. V, nos. 3 and 4, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - The Pulp Collector, vol. 2, no. 1, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Reader's Digest, vol. 17, no. 102; vol. 19, no. 111, 1930, 1931 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Reader's Digest, vol. 24, no. 143; vol. 27, no. 162, 1934, 1935 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Salmagundi, no. 54, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - San Francisco Review of Books, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - "Science and Civilisation in China" by Joseph Needham, 1961 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Scribner's Magazine, vol. IX, no.3, 1891 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Scribner's Monthly, vol. XVII, no. 4, 1879 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - The Seattle Review, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Secret Service, 1908, 1911, 1917 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Shocks, issue 5, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Trapped by a Woman, by Nicholas Carter, 1905 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - True Detective Mysteries, 1929 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Uncle Sam-ee and his Little Chi-nee, 1878 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - The Unicorn, vol. I, no. 4 - "The Shadow" issue, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - The Union Jack, 1921, 1923 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - The Union Jack 2D, nos. 1057, 1063, 1315, 1495, 1924, 1928, 1932 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - War Novels Magazine, vol. I, no. 1, 1952 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - The Yellow Peril: 1890-1924, chapters 1-5, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - The Yellow Peril: 1890-1924, chapters 6-10, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - The Yellow Peril: 1890-1924, chapters 11-end, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Yellow Silk, issue 33, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - "Issei, Nissei, Sansei: Japanese in America" bibliography and related materials [Flat Box], 1971 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - "Ten Drawings in Chinatown with Certain Observations" by Robert Howe Fletcher [Flat Box], 1898 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Series VI: Yoshio Kishi's Files
  This series contains computer printouts of online auctions, newsletters, brochures, catalogues and price lists, periodicals, price guides, photocopied articles and book chapters, screenplays and writings by Yoshio Kishi, and other materials Kishi collected on Asian Americans.
  - Subseries A: Vince Lombardi
    - Biographical info on Lombardi, Undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - "Lombardi Drills on Self-Control", Newspaper article in the New York Times, Undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Lombardi - expense report, Undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - "Lombardi" script, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Lombardi interview transcriptions, Undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Lombardi-isms, Undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - "Lombardi" narration script, 1968, Undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Lombardi - schedule, film outline, other material, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Notes on NFL Draft, Lombardi fan letters, St. Marks Rectory, and Lombardi's pep talk for the superbowl, 1968, Undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Source Material for "Lombardi", Undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Sport Magazine with article on "Why Vince Lombardi is a Winner", 1968 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Subseries B: Collected Articles
    - "Across the Continent" by Samuel Bowles, 1865 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Putnam's Magazine, 1868 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - "Beyond the Mississippi" by Albert D. Richardson, 1867 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - The Japan Times Overland Mail, 1868, 1869 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Putnam's Magazine, 1869 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Putnam's Magazine, 1869 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Atlantic Monthly, vol. 24, 1869 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Report of the Governer of Wyoming to the Secretary of the Interior, 1885 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - The Japan Weekly Mail, 1870-1893 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Scribner's, 1870 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - "Garnered Sheaves" by Albert D. Richardson, 1871 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - "The Chinese Problem" by L.T. Townsend, 1876 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Six Chinese Companies, Memorial, 1877 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - "The Battle of the Wabash" by Lorelle, 1880 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - "Congressional Record - Senate", "Congressional Record - House", 1882 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - "Chinese Immigration: A Sociological Study" by Gerrit L. Lansing, 1882 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - "Through Cities and Prairie Lands" by Lady Duffy Hardy (photocopy), 1882 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - "Our Police Protectors" by A.E. Costello, 1884 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - "Samantha at the Centennial" by Marietta Holley, 1884 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Wyoming, Rock Springs, 1885 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Municipal Reports for the Fiscal Year 1884-1885, San Francisco, CA (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - "Nature and People of Japan" by W.E. Griffis, 1889 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - "The Pacific Coast Scenic Tour" by Henry T. Finck, 1890 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - "Traveling Alone: A Woman's Journey Around the World", Leland, 1890 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - U.S. Congress - "Letter from the Secretary of Treasury...", 1890 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - "Pioneer Days in California" by John Carr, 1891 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - "The Sacking of Grubville" by Adah Fairbanks Batelle, 1892 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - "The Year 1899" by William Ward Crane, 1893 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - "Our Brother in Yellow" by L.A. Banks, 1893 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - "The Pacific Coast Pulpit" by Irwin, 1893 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - "California Sketches" by O.P. Fitzgerald, 1896 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - "A Flying Visit to the American Continent" by F. Dale Pawle, 1896 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - "Historical Abstract of San Francisco" by Oscar T. Shuck, 1897 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - "Ten Drawings of Chinatown" by Ernest C. Peixotto, 1898 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - The Japan Times, 1899 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - "The Chinese Immigrant in...Asia" F.W. Williams, 1900 (Box 20, Folder 36)
    - "The Unlawful and Unjustifiable..." by Francis A. Brooks, 1901 (Box 20, Folder 37)
    - Report of the Commission on Chinese, 1902 (Box 20, Folder 38)
    - "Exclusion of Japanese and Chinese from American Territory, 1902 (Box 20, Folder 39)
    - The Critic, 1904 (Box 20, Folder 40)
    - "Select List of References on Chinese Immigration", Griffin, 1904 (Box 20, Folder 41)
    - "A Digest of the Treaty, Laws, and Regulations Governing the Admission of Chinese" by Frederick D. Cloud, 1908 (Box 20, Folder 42)
    - "The Treatment of the Exempt Classes of Chinese in the United States"b y Ng Poon Chew, 1908 (Box 20, Folder 43)
    - "Commonwealth vs. Nin Sing et al.", 1908 (Box 20, Folder 44)
    - The Buffalo Bill Stories, no. 402, 1909 (Box 20, Folder 45)
    - "The Revelation" by R.J. Pearsall, 1911 (Box 20, Folder 46)
    - "Retrisoection" by Hubert How Bancroft, 1912 (Box 20, Folder 47)
    - "The Valley of the Moon" by Jack London, 1913 (Box 20, Folder 48)
    - U.S. Department of Labor Treaties, Laws, and Rules, 1914 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - The Literary Digest, 1918 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - "Lament for the Dime Novel" by Cobb, 1921 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - "Facts about Japanese in Canada", 1922 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - "American Nights Entertainment" by Grant Overton, 1923 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Exerpts from "Travel" - The Outline of Knowledge, vol. XV, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - "White Night Lights" by O.O. McIntyre, 1924 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - Unlabeled articles, 1925-1986, Undated (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - Westwards, vol. 1, no. 6, 1928 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - "Wanderings of the Japanese Beyond the Seas" by V. Posdneeff, 1929 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - "The Real New York" by Helen Worden, 1932 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - "The Resurrection of Chin Lee", 1941 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - The New York Times, 1942, 1971-1990 (Box 20, Folder 61)
    - Akiya - miscellaneous, 1943-1944, Undated (Box 20, Folder 62)
    - "The Best Plays of 1899-1909, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 63)
    - Bibliography on the Japanese in American Agriculture, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 64)
    - The Journal of Educational Society, vol. 22, no. 5, 1949 (Box 20, Folder 65)
    - Pacific Citizen, 1953, 1984, 1985, 1989, 1990, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 66)